<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>参考文献 on Tan Jay | 唐 洁</title>
    <link>/tags/%E5%8F%82%E8%80%83%E6%96%87%E7%8C%AE/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 参考文献 on Tan Jay | 唐 洁</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/tags/%E5%8F%82%E8%80%83%E6%96%87%E7%8C%AE/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>SDPD</title>
      <link>/cn/sdpd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Tan Jay</author>
      <guid>/cn/sdpd/</guid>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
        <h2 id="empirical-likelihood-for-spatial-dynamic-panel-data-models-with-spatial-errors-and-endogenous-initial-observations">Empirical likelihood for spatial dynamic panel data models with spatial errors and endogenous initial observations</h2>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Anselin, L. (1988). <em>patial Econometrics: Methods and Models</em>. Amsterdam: Kluwer Academic Publishers.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Anselin, L. (2001). Spatial econometrics. <a href="http://www.onacademic.com/detail/journal_1000039480956210_65cc.html">In: Baltagi, B. H. (Ed.), <em>A Companion to Theoretical Econometrics</em>. Blackwell Publishers Ltd., Massachusetts, 310-330.</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Anselin, L., Le Gallo, J., &amp; Jayet, H. (2008). Spatial panel econometrics. <a href="http://library.oum.edu.my/oumlib/content/catalog/691963">In: Mátyás, L., Sevestre, P. (Eds.), <em>The Econometrics of Panel Data: Fundamentals and Recent Developments in Theory and Practice</em>. SpringerVerlag, Berlin Heidelberg, 625-660.</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Baltagi, B.H., Song, S.H., &amp; Koh, W. (2003). Testing panel data regression models with spatial error correlation. <em>Journal of Econometrics, 117</em>, 123-150.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Baltagi, B.H., Egger, P., &amp; Pfaffermayr, M. (2013). A generalized spatial panel data model with random effects. <em>Econometric Reviews, 32</em>, 650-685.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Bandyopadhyay, S., Lahiri, N., &amp; Nordman, D. J. (2015). A frequency domain empirical likelihood method for irregularly spaced spatial data. <em>Annals of Statistics, 43</em>, 519-545.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Bhargava, A., &amp; Sargan, J.D. (1983). Estimating dynamic random effects models from panel data covering short time periods. <em>Econometrica, 51</em>, 1635-1659.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Chen, S. X., &amp; Keilegom, I. V. (2009). A review on empirical likelihood methods for regression. <em>Test, 18</em>, 415-447.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Chen, J., &amp; Qin, J. (1993). Empirical likelihood estimation for finite populations and the effective usage of auxiliary information. <em>Biometrika, 80</em>, 107-116.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Cliff, A. D., &amp; Ord, J. K. (1973). <em>Spatial autocorrelation</em>. London: Pion Ltd.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Cressien, N. (1993). <em>Statistics for spatial data</em>. New York: Wiley.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Elhorst, J.P. (2003). Specification and estimation of spatial panel data models. <em>International Regional Science Review , 26</em>, 244-268.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Elhorst, J.P. (2012). Dynamic spatial panels: models, methods, and inferences. <em>Journal of geographical systems, 14</em>, 5-28.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Hsiao, C. (2003). <em>Analysis of Panel Data, second ed.</em>. Cambridge University Press, Cambridge.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Hsiao, C., Pesaran, M.H., &amp; Tahmiscioglu, A.K. (2002). Maximum likelihood estimation
of fixed effects dynamic panel data models covering short time periods. <em>Econometrics, 109</em>, 107-150.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Jin, F., Lee, &amp; L. F. (2019). GEL estimation and tests of spatial autoregressive models. <em>Journal of Econometrics, 208</em>, 585-612.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Kelejian, H. H., &amp; Prucha, L. R. (1998). A generalized spatial two-stage least squares procedure for estimating a spatial autoregressive model with autoregressive disturbances. <em>The Journal of Real Estate Finance and Economics, 17</em>, 99-121.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Kelejian, H. H., &amp; Prucha, L. R. (1999). A generalized moments estimator for the autoregressive parameter in a spatial model. <em>International Economic Review, 40</em>, 509-533.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Kelejian, H.H., &amp; Prucha, I.R. (2001). On the asymptotic distribution of the Moran I test statistic with applications. <em>Econometrics, 104</em>, 219-257.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Kelejian, H. H., Prucha, I. R., &amp; Yuzefovich, Y. (2004). Instrumental variable estimation of a spatial autoregressive model with autoregressive disturbances: large and small sample results. <em>Spatial and Spatiotemporal Econometrics, 18</em>, 163-198.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Kelejian, H. H., &amp; Prucha, I. R. (2006). HAC estimation in a spatial framework. <em>Journal of Econometrics, 140</em>, 131-154.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Kolaczyk, E. D. (1994). Emprical likelihood for generalized linear models. <em>Statistica Sinica, 4</em>, 199-218.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Lee, L.F., &amp; Yu, J. (2010). A spatial dynamic panel data model with both time and individual fixed effects. <em>Econometric Theory, 26</em>, 564-597.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Lee, L.F., &amp; Yu, J. (2016). Identification of Spatial Durbin Panel Models. <em>Applied Economics, 31</em>, 133-162.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Li, Y. H., Li, Y., &amp; Qin, Y. S. (2020). Empirical likelihood for panel data models with spatial errors. <em>Communications in Statistics-Theory and Methods, 51</em>, 2838-2857.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Liu, X., Lee, L. F., &amp; Bollinger, C. R. (2010). An efficient GMM estimator of spatial autoregressive models. <em>Journal of Econometrics, 159</em>, 303-319.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Nordman, D. J. (2008). An empirical likelihood method for spatial regression. <em>Metrika, 68</em>, 351-363.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Owen, A. B. (1988).  Empirical likelihood ratio confidence intervals for a single functional. <em>Biometrika, 75</em>, 237-249.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Owen, A. B. (1990). Empirical likelihood ratio confidence regions. <em>Annals of Statistics, 18</em>, 90-120.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Owen, A. B. (1991). Empirical likelihood for linear models. <em>Annals of Statistics, 19</em>, 1725-1747.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Owen, A. B. (2001). <em>Empirical Likelihood</em>. New York: Chapman &amp; Hall.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Parent, O., &amp; LeSage, J.P. (2011). A space-time filter for panel data models containing random effects. <em>Computational Statistics &amp; Data Analysis, 55</em>, 475-490.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Parent, O., &amp; LeSage, J.P. (2012). Spatial dynamic panel data models with random effects. <em>Regional Science and Urban Economics, 42</em>, 727-738.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Qin, Y. S. (1999). Empirical likelihood ratio confidence regions in a partly linear model. <em>Chinese Journal of applied probability and statistics, 15</em>, 363-369.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Qin, J., &amp; Lawless, J. (1994). Empirical likelihood and general estimating equations. <em>Annals of Statistics, 22</em>, 300-325.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Qin, Y. S. (2021). Empirical likelihood for spatial autoregressive models with spatial autoregressive disturbances. <em>Sankhyā A: Indian J. Statist., 83</em>, 1-25.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Qin, Y. S., &amp; Lei, Q. Z. (2021). Empirical likelihood for mixed regressive, spatial autoregressive model based on GMM. <em>Sankhyā A: Indian J. Statist., 83</em>, 353-378.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Rong, J. R., Liu, Y., &amp; Qin, Y. S. (2021). Empirical likelihood for spatial dynamic panel data models with spatial lags and spatial errors. <em>Communications in Statistics-Theory and Methods</em>. <a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/03610926.2022.2032172">https://doi.org/10.1080/03610926.2022.2032172</a>.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Qu, X., Lee, L.F., &amp; Yu, J. (2017). QML estimation of spatial dynamic panel data models with endogenous time varying spatial weights matrices. <em>Econometrics, 197</em>, 173-201.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Su, L., &amp; Yang, Z. (2007). QML estimation of dynamic panel data models with spatial errors. <em>Singapore Management University manuscript</em>.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Su, L., &amp; Yang, Z. (2015). QML estimation of dynamic panel data models with spatial errors. <em>Econometrics, 185</em>, 230-258.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Wu, C.B. (2004). Weighted empirical likelihood inference. <em>Statistics &amp; Probability Letters, 66</em>, 67-79.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Yang, Z., Li, C., &amp; Tse, Y.K. (2006). Functional form and spatial dependence in dynamic panels. <em>Economics Letters, 91</em>, 138-145.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Yu, J., R, de Jong., &amp; Lee, L.F. (2008). Quasi-maximum likelihood estimators for spatial dynamic panel data with fixed effects when both <em>n</em> and <em>T</em> are large. <em>Journal of Econometrics, 146</em>, 118-134.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Zhong, B., &amp; Rao, J. N. K. (2000). Empirical likelihood inference under stratified random sampling using auxiliary population information. <em>Biometrika, 87</em>, 929-938.</p>
</li>
</ol>

        
        ]]>
      </description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
